mytrip.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Mytrip.com

At Mytrip.com we understand that data privacy is a very important issue. Mytrip.com is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal details every time you make purchases online, and considers customer information safety a matter of great importance. This policy explains how we use customer information and how we protect your privacy. Please read it carefully. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy: 

* How we use your information 
* Sharing your information with third parties 
* How we protect your information 
* Children's privacy 
* Links 
* Changes to this privacy policy 
* Contact 

## What kind of information we collect

**In General.** We receive and collect any kind of information you provide us. This includes information that can identify you ( "Personal Information"), including name and surname, telephone number and your e-mail. We also collect information about the transactions you realize including your credit card number, name of the card holder and expiry date. We may collect additional information regarding your travel preferences, including meal requests, seat request as well as the frequent flyer/hotel/car rental program information. You can even choose not to provide additional information. However, some information is necessary in order to complete a purchase through our website, to participate in surveys or contests or to send us a question related to your booking. 

**Passenger information.** When you make a purchase through Mytrip.com, we collect your travel preferences. Your profile is updated and enriched every time you use Mytrip.com.

**Automatic collection of information.** We automatically collect certain information about your computer when you visit Mytrip.com. For example, we collect information regarding the browser you use (eg Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, etc.) and IP address. We may also collect information about your activity on our site, including information such as trips viewed and purchases made. The main goal of collecting this automatic information is to understand the user's experience in our site.

**Cookies.** When you visit Mytrip.com, we send to your computer a "cookie". Cookies are information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. They enable Mytrip.com to provide features and preferences based on your last flight search so as to make future searches faster. Note that all information contained in cookies is encrypted for security reasons. You can always choose not to receive cookies from Mytrip.com, just note that in this case you might not be able to access and use some of the tools offered by Mytrip.com or complete a purchase successfully.

## How we use your information

Personal data such as the name of the card holder, credit card number, expiry date and CVV are required to complete the booking process through our site. We will use your information to improve and personalize our service. We will also use your contact details for communication purposes, in case we need to contact you. We may also use your information to send you offers and news about Mytrip.com products and services or those of other carefully selected companies which we think that they may be of your interest. We may also use and analyze the information that we collect so that we can improve our services. 

## Sharing your information

Mytrip.com may share your information with the following entities: 

* **Suppliers** , such as hotels, airlines, ferry companies and car rental agencies who offer the final service of the reservations realized through our site. We do not share your e-mail address with these suppliers unless they need it to complete your booking or in case that a problem occurs. Generally the information provided to suppliers is limited to the required extent for a successfully completed booking. These suppliers may also contact you, if necessary, to obtain additional information or to facilitate the process of your travel reservation. 
* **Business Units** are affiliates of the company **E-travel SA** including **Mytrip.com. The affiliate sites** [Pamediakopes.gr](http://www.pamediakopes.gr/), [FantasticGreece.com ](http://www.fantasticgreece.com/), [Mytrip.com](http://www.mytrip.com/), [Athenshotels.gr](http://www.athenshotels.gr/), [moneyexpert.gr](http://www.moneyexpert.gr/) have access to your information and may also send you details of other products and services which we consider of your interest. These companies follow the same privacy policy as this one presented here. 
* We may also share anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of users of our site or the most popular holiday destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and it is used for research purposes only. 

## How we protect your information

We take all the necessary security measures to protect your personal data against unauthorized access or/and alteration, disclosure and destruction. We use all the necessary administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect the personal information you provide us. For example, only authorized employees may access your personal information. In addition, we use encryption during the transmission of your personal information across the internet as well as firewalls and intrusion detection systems to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information. 

## Children' s privacy

Mytrip.com does not sell travel or other services to children. If a child under 18 years old attempts to make a purchase through Mytrip.com, we will use his/her personal information only to inform the child that we need parental permission so as we complete the reservation. 

## External links

Mytrip.com may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. 

## Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at +44 8447747881
